(This program is intended
for viewers aged 18 and over.)
(It may contain content
depicting inappropriate behavior)
(violence, sexual content,
and strong language.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
(This series is entirely fictional
and does not depict)
(any real individuals, locations,
organizations, or events.)
(WARNING: This episode contains
flashing lights and strobe effects)
(that may trigger seizures
in viewers with photosensitive epilepsy.)
♪Birthday but with me♪
♪Every time, it's just me and me only♪
♪What's this feeling? I've got no clue,♪
♪Could it be I'm missing you?♪
♪(Am I missing you?)♪
♪Birthday but with me♪
♪Why is it always happening to me?♪
♪The more it happens, the more I see♪
♪Yeah, it must be♪
(We are B.S. Brothers)
I know we're all
eyeing that championship,
but no matter how things turn out,
I just want us to have fun together.
We've been through a lot.
- We've got nothing left to lose.
- You're right.
Our fun is their downfall.
Heck yeah!
This year's dark horse
- is us, B.S. Brothers!
- Exactly.
- Let's smash them to pieces!
- Hell yeah!
- B.S. Brothers!
- Talk your sh*t, take the championship!
Whoa, holy sh*t!
There are so many people.
Damn, she's so cute.
(Good luck, P'Three!)
Man, thinking about it just bums me out.
If Beauty hadn't ghosted me,
I'd be showing off a girl
all over this place by now.
You're upset, aren't you?
Instead of showing off a girl,
you're stuck with me again.
Showing you off...
doesn't sound too bad.
Uh, excuse me.
Can I interview you two for my channel?
- Interview me?
- Yes.
I'm actually not great with cameras,
but since the interviewer is cute,
I'll let you ask a few questions.
I'll start now, then.
First question.
Who are you here with?
Oh, I'm here with a friend.
And which team are you
and your friend cheering for today?
Of course I'm here
to cheer for my best friend.
He's a member of B.S. Brothers.
B.S. Brothers!
- Hi, everyone!
- Hello!
So handsome!
You're even cuter in person, Soh.
Not really.
Thank you.
Will you be doing a face reveal
during the match today?
Yeah, since it's the offline match,
can't you just play
without the bear head?
Well, I...
I think...
It's better if you keep it on.
If you take it off,
I won't be able to look away from you.
How are you supposed to focus,
right, P'Three?
Exactly! You won, Soh.
Don't take it off
for P'Three's sake, little bear.
Blue Viper!
- Aw!
- Aw, look!
That's Blue Viper.
I already invited them,
but they didn't want to come.
What? I didn't even ask you anything.
Make them regret it.
Regret not coming to see you play.
Bring home that trophy.
- Got it?
- Yeah, I know.
Alright, I'll be watching
from the crowd.
- Yeah, just get lost.
- I'm off.
They probably know
that coming here
would be a waste of time.
Oh...
At least it's good that
your brother's here today,
because if he'd come tomorrow,
you wouldn't even be in the lineup.
Why?
Are you barking just 'cause...
you've been rotting
on the bench for too long?
Are you that repressed?
I've been wondering, Three.
The reason Soh has to put up
with that stifling bear head
is because of you, isn't it?
What the hell are you talking about?
I told you to stay away from him.
If you hadn't sent a hate mob after him,
or if he had never met you,
he wouldn't have had to put up
with all this for your sake.
Let me tell you something.
The person you should be afraid of...
isn't me or Soh.
It's yourself,
the guy who does sh*tty things
to people without even realizing it.
Hello, Mom?
Okay, sure.
Alright, the wait is almost over.
Today's showdown is between
two teams from the lower bracket.
One of them is the fourth-place team,
B.S. Brothers,
who are making their first appearance
in this tournament.
They'll be facing off
against the third-place team,
Apex Sharkz.
And the match is about to begin.
Are you okay, P'Three?
If Soh had never met you,
he wouldn't have had to put up
with all this for your sake.
Yeah.
I'm okay.
And this match
has incredibly high stakes,
higher than Mount Everest itself,
because the losing team
will have their season end immediately.
That's right. Whoever loses here
is going straight home immediately.
There are no second chances.
As for the winner,
they'll face the loser
of the upper bracket
to decide who advances
to the Grand Final.
(Good luck, P'Three!)
Sorry. Excuse me.
Sorry.
Please cheer for B.S. Brothers.
Please cheer for them.
Cheer for B.S. Brothers.
And the first game is about to begin.
So, let's head into the match!
Alright, the match has started.
The B.S. Brothers crew
is heading straight into the jungle.
They're invading aggressively,
and they've secured the Blue Buff.
Whoa, they're roaming in and out
like it's their own backyard.
The enemy jungler must be like,
"Those are my creeps, P'Three!"
Enough already. I can't handle this.
Man, looking at
B.S. Brothers' gold...
If they're just snowballing
and extending that lead,
Apex Sharkz might not even
make it to the late game.
Three's spotted someone with low HP,
and it's just too tempting for him.
Wait, isn't that a bit too far?
The bushes are packed with enemies!
P'Three, watch out! Fall back.
Whoa, and that was it. He got baited.
He got burst down in a single combo.
- Nice, nice!
- Nice work! Keep going.
Reset, reset. Relax, bro.
Here we go again.
Three is forcing the play
and going way too far.
They had the lead in the early game,
but they're now falling behind.
Momentum has shifted
back to Apex Sharkz.
P'Three, stay calm. Let's reset.
Three, reset now.
Is he soloing the Slayer?
- Go, go. He's alone!
- He is. Let's get it.
- He's all over the place. Go for it.
- Go, go, go!
And in this moment,
Three's decided to
solo the God Slayer
while his teammates
are still busy clearing waves.
Wait, the enemy team
has hit all their power spikes!
What are they doing?
P'Three, fall back! We're not ready yet.
Don't force it,
or we'll lose the whole game.
Yeah, I'll make it.
I can secure it.
No, you won't make it.
Leave the Slayer!
P'Three!
And it's over.
That was a devastating blow.
They've lost both the Slayer
and their Jungler.
Is this going to be the end
of the first game?
- Nice! Go, go.
- Here we go!
We're doing a great job.
- Hey!
- Wait...
- Hey, Three!
- P'Three!
Wait, something's off.
- Why is he so off?
- I have no idea.
It's okay, guys.
This is only the first game.
We still have a chance
to turn this around.
Don't worry. Just focus and try again.
If something's on your mind,
you can talk to me.
You know, don't you,
that scientists have said
that a hug...
can make you feel happier?
You don't have to wait
for me to count to three.
You can just come hug me and recharge...
Sometimes, I think...
that if you hadn't met me,
things might have been better.
I...
I'm so damn selfish.
If I hadn't dragged you into this,
you probably...
wouldn't have to endure
wearing this bear head.
I'm sorry, Soh.
That's true.
I had to wear this bear head
because of you.
But today,
I chose to wear it myself.
Do you remember...
what I once told you,
that I didn't want to use a webcam
while streaming?
It's because I thought the viewers
wanted to see the game, not my face.
But the truth is,
I was just scared,
scared of being judged,
and scared that the pressure
would stop me from having fun.
This bear head...
shields me from everyone's eyes.
It makes me feel safe
without having to worry
about people staring at me.
It makes me feel like...
I'm back playing games for fun
alone in my room.
And...
this bear head...
doesn't make me feel stifled at all.
Instead, it gives me...
the courage to stand by your side
and fight together.
So...
Please don't overthink it, P'Three.
The reason I chose this bear head...
is because I chose you.
Thanks, Soh.
No matter what happens,
we'll get through it together.
Whoa...
B.S. ...
- Brothers!
(Good luck, P'Three!)
We're here to cheer for P'Three!
You've got this, P'Three!
B.S. ...
- Brothers!
(Creeps spawning in 5 seconds)
What the hell?
Hey, we can take them now.
Soh, go initiate. I'll follow up.
- Laem, zone one off me.
- You got it.
Dive in! I've got them locked down.
- Nice!
- Perfect.
Hey, there's only one left!
- Go for it!
- Yeah!
Finish them!
(The Red Team's tower
has been destroyed)
Way to go, B.S. Brothers!
Ambush!
- Group up!
- Grouping up!
In the same bush, yeah.
- Preaw, go bait them.
- Hold on, wait.
Just like that.
Someone's coming.
- Go, go, go! This is it.
- Alright, let's hit it!
(The Red Team's tower
has been destroyed)
- Whoa...
- That's it!
Hell yeah! Keep those wins coming.
And at this match point
for B.S. Brothers,
will they end
Apex Sharkz's run right here?
They're playing so cracked.
- Chill out.
- Sorry. My bad.
And now, they just need to
finish the objectives.
Just finish the base 'cause winning
means taking down the base, kids!
- Get in there!
- Yeah.
(The Red Team's tower has been destroyed)
Keep pushing.
Now what?
And now,
the team moving on to face
the loser of the upper bracket tomorrow
is...
- B.S. Brothers!
B.S. Brothers, baby!
B.S. Brothers!
What the hell?
Damn it!
Play like we practiced!
- Just play the way we practiced!
- No, you said don't go too far.
F*ck!
Sh*t, they're real dark horses.
How did that happen?
Look, even if they qualify,
they're not gonna make it anyway.
They've finally made it!
This is the ultimate dark horse team
in the RoV Pro League 2026 Summer!
That's incredible.
After being looked down upon
for several seasons
and consistently being out of form,
people thought they were finished.
But they've made a comeback!
Like I always say, the comeback is real.
This is B.S. Brothers!
Be careful.
Come on.
One, two, three!
Man, I only made it because of you guys.
Thanks for carrying me.
Hey, what are you talking about?
We didn't do that.
Yeah, we won because of teamwork.
- Exactly.
- Hey.
No one's carrying anyone here.
We just have each other's backs.
Great job, Captain.
Thank you.
Thank you so much
for choosing to stand by me.
P'Three, you're everything to me.
Just hug each other.
We won!
- Go, go, go!
- Let's dance.
- They're not joining us.
- Come on.
- To the right.
- Let's go.
To the left. Now, to the right.
That was insane.
You've got some serious luck.
More luck than skill, obviously.
I really have to hand it
to your trash-talking skills, Ten.
Say whatever the hell you want
because the person
you're trying to use as my weakness
is actually my greatest strength.
(And for Blue Viper's results,)
(the MVP award goes to Peem.)
(Whoa, well deserved for THE PEEM.)
(He carried the team so hard.
Not sure if that wore him out.)
(The MVP,
or the Most Valuable Player...)
Wait.
Stay with me for a bit.
Thought we were gonna be strangers
until the tournament ends?
What kind of strangers smoke together?
Can't strangers just smoke
in the same spot?
Your playstyle
was annoying as hell today.
So annoying that I don't even
want to see your face anymore.
Well, you're free to keep being annoyed.
Tomorrow's the final.
Get ready to face my team.
I really want to put you in your place
and snuff out your confidence
just like this cigarette.
Ten...
You can give it back to me
after the final.
Dive in, dive in!
- Play the lanes.
- This is easy.
- You shouldn't have died just now.
- Yeah, focus.
Yeah.
Don't lose your mind just yet.
- Jay, call the play!
- Hey, help me out over here.
P'Jay, open the map.
Dammit.
- Push, push!
- Go!
Wait, wait for the power spike.
Don't go in just to die.
- Fall back, then!
- Don't go out and feed.
- Get out!
- Pull back!
I told you so.
What a waste.
- This sucks.
- Yeah.
This is so frustrating.
- Damn...
- Forget it.
We gave it our all, didn't we?
Third place isn't that bad.
They're really cracked this year.
I mean...
Let's try again next year.
Hey, but I think...
Stop right there.
I'm already losing my mind as it is.
Hey.
Guess you're not just
a "bullsh*t" team anymore.
Go and take that championship,
B.S. Brothers.
- See you.
- See ya.
From this angle,
the stage is pretty grand, isn't it?
If we get to stand up there,
it would be so cool.
I finally managed to make it up there,
but in the end,
they still didn't come to see me.
I know I've had
such a big ego in the past
to make a stand against my family
that I wouldn't show my face
until I succeeded.
But now that I'm actually here,
I don't want to wait until I succeed
just to show off anymore.
I already invited them,
but they didn't want to come.
I just want them to see
how much effort
I've put in along the way.
Just wait a little longer, P'Three.
I'll help you take that trophy home
to show your family.
When that time comes,
I believe...
that they'll be proud
to have a son who is this talented
and hardworking.
Oh, please.
Wow, you're really fired up.
Where are you getting
all this confidence from?
Ow, P'Three!
You're pinching my cheeks way too hard.
Thanks, Soh.
Even if we don't win the trophy,
I've got a reward just for you.
And you think you're the only one
who has a surprise?
Whoa.
Are you surprising me back?
Or are you just throwing
my own words back at me?
Hey, you're ignoring me?
Soh, what is it?
What are you giving me?
What is it? A microwave?
Where did everyone go?
Your voice got here before you did.
A quick walk after that meal
made me feel much better.
Jeez.
- Keep those eyes wide open, though.
- Exactly.
- Come on, cheer up!
- Cheer up.
The match is in 40 minutes, guys.
Come on, guys.
- Here we go.
- Let's go.
Alright.
- Ready.
- Yeah.
Wait.
What are you looking for?
My bear head.
Where's my bear head?
Look for it, guys. Hurry.
Move it, look around.
Did you check over there?
P'Jack, found it?
No.
It's Ten, that bastard.
- Hey! Three!
- Three!
- Come on, follow him.
- P'Three!
- Ten, you bastard!
- Three!
Where did you put the bear head?
What the hell is wrong with you?
Can you drop
the sh*tty attitude for once
and just follow the rules?
Is that too hard
for your tiny brain to handle?
Why don't you take a good look
at yourself first?
Barging into another team's room,
you call that following the rules?
And what about back then?
You sold your own team's strategies
to the rivals.
Do you call that following the rules?
That's enough.
I'll radio the security guards
at the different posts for you,
but I have to be honest...
With this many people
and so little time left,
I think you'd better get ready
for the match instead.
In that case, can I ask
to delay the match just a little bit?
I'll coordinate that for you,
but there's only so much
we can delay it.
Otherwise, it'll throw off
the entire schedule.
Got it. I understand.
Thank you very much.
Don't worry, Soh.
I've bought us some time.
Everyone's looking for it right now.
We'll find it soon.
And what if we don't?
If I don't have that bear head,
I definitely won't be able to play.
What if I lose my focus
and cost the team the match?
You've worked so hard
to get to this point.
What if it's all ruined because of me?
Proving myself to my family
does matter to me,
but what matters most right now
isn't that anymore.
It's about how you feel.
Now, my boy.
What did you just tell me?
No matter what happens,
we'll get through it together.
I'm only standing here today
because of you.
So...
today,
you're going to get through this, too.
Up there on stage...
with me standing beside you,
it's safer than having the bear head on.
Or...
want to use my muscles
to shield your face?
Alright, everyone. Welcome...
to the RoV Pro League 2026 Summer.
- And this is the Grand Final!
- The Grand Final!
Whoa, my apologies.
There's been a slight delay
in the match,
but the excitement is guaranteed
to be worth it.
It always has to be us, huh?
Somehow, trouble always finds us.
Even though the schedule
has been pushed back,
the action is exactly as promised.
We're ready to serve up the fun to you.
But right now, the fans...
Wait, I can barely hear the crowd.
Hello? Let's hear some noise
from the crowd!
We're about to head into
the Grand Final.
Make some noise!
Here is the moment
you've been waiting for.
It's time for the Grand Final.
RPL Summer 2026 is about to kick off!
Alright, now, let's meet...
the final two teams
heading into the Grand Final:
Blue Viper and B.S. Brothers!
Wait, hold on a second.
Is that Soh, Derya MK12?
Whoa, Soh is doing a face reveal!
Damn, revealing it now?
He must be dead serious.
But why does he look so pale?
A face reveal?
Will he be able to focus?
- I know, right?
- Yeah.
Sh*t...
Come on.
Let's do it.
Guys...
This is the moment
everyone's been waiting for.
The overlooked dark horse,
B.S. Brothers,
has successfully made it to face
the defending champion, Blue Viper.
Keep an eye on the key players
from both teams.
It'll be either Three or Ten
rising to the top
of the RPL Summer 2026 tonight.
Without further ado, let's get into it!
(Welcome to Arena of Valor)
- Dive in!
- Got it.
Just push forward.
Soh, look out!
Soh! Soh...
- Clean play!
- Nice.
- Great.
- They suck.
It's okay, Soh.
Just reset.
Let's try again.
Soh, calm down, bro.
- Get him. He's being so cocky.
- Almost there.
Combo! Combo!
(Seriously? Is this the same Derya
in the bear head?)
(Too many conditions.
Get a new Support next season.)
(For real.)
(Ugh, B.S. Brothers...
They're losing because of the Support.)
Can you hear me, Soh?
Soh!
Remember what I told you?
If you're still scared
once you're up on that stage,
then don't look at them.
Just think of it
as if no one is watching us.
We're just sitting comfortably
in our most comfortable spot.
If you still feel unsure,
then look right here.
I'm right here,
and I have total confidence in you.
I do, too.
Me too.
Me three.
I also trust you.
- So do we.
Forget everyone else...
and just be my Player Two.
Blue Viper is looking to dive
and pick off Derya first.
In a three-on-one like this,
he's unlikely to survive.
Dive in! Now, go for it.
What a play!
- Hey, fall back!
- He dodged and countered with a single burst.
They're totally scattered!
And now Blue Viper
is forced into a long retreat.
Great job, Soh.
Yeah, push it! This is our chance.
Play it safe. Fall back for now.
Can we counter?
Fall back. It's no good.
Don't. Let's just retreat.
Fall back.
Whoa, this is the Derya we all know!
If you think he can't perform
without the bear head,
well, think again.
- Yeah, almost there.
- Just a little bit more.
Push, push!
- Hey, hey!
- Come on, let's go!
The creeps are here!
Let's end the game!
With the creeps pushing in,
will B.S. Brothers
be able to close it out?
And...
Sh*t! Where are you going?
- Defend the base!
- I'm heading back.
- Hang on, I'm on my way.
- Hurry up, damn it!
And the first game
goes to B.S. Brothers!
What on earth just happened?
We've got the first game!
Sh*t.
I couldn't escape.
Wait for Preaw.
Get the Dark Slayer!
- On it.
- Get in here!
Hey, they're invading our jungle.
Fall back, then. Don't force it.
Don't do it.
- Go for it! I've got this.
- Dive in!
- I've got it.
- I'm taking care of it.
Tank for me.
P'Three, help me out!
Can we fall back in time?
It's alright. Let's go again.
- Yeah, try again.
- Do it again.
Let's go again!
Wait for Preaw to respawn.
Man, looks like another bad call
from ten10 right there.
He's being too aggressive,
and it's costing him.
He's really off his game today.
He's usually better. He's putting
too much pressure on himself.
(The Red Team's tower has been destroyed)
Dive in! Go, go.
- Let's end this!
- End it!
Finish them!
Just like that.
Blue Viper isn't all that after all!
And in the sixth game,
B.S. Brothers took the win,
tying it up at 3-3!
Wow, it's a dead heat.
You pr*ck!
You messed up again.
What the hell did I do?
What kind of sh*tty play was that?
Split pushing all by yourself,
and you couldn't even
break the tower, dammit.
And why didn't you help me?
Hey, enough!
Sh*t, like you're the only one
who's good.
You'll see, Ten.
And finally,
we've reached the ultimate conclusion.
This is the seventh game.
Most importantly, whoever wins this
will be the RPL Summer 2026 champion.
(Abyssal Dragon has been defeated)
That's nice! Keep it going!
- Dammit!
- I'm on my way!
Three up top! Group top!
Yeah, I'm going!
Their Dark Slayer Laner
is in our jungle.
Looks like Blue Viper
wants to end this quickly.
They're all rotating top.
They're definitely gunning for JJack.
They're planning to pressure this lane
all the way.
Keep pushing! Come on!
(The Blue Team's tower
has been destroyed)
Ten, you're low! Recall already!
No retreat.
We can end this. Follow me.
Sh*t, they're unstoppable!
Ladies and gentlemen,
it looks like
the situation for B.S. Brothers
is far from easy now.
And it seems like making a comeback
with no towers left like this
is almost impossible.
In other words, the other team's
chances of losing are slim to none.
Jack, target the backline!
- On it.
- Yeah.
Hey, they're all in! They're all in!
- Help me out!
- Whoa!
Whoa! A hellish counter-combo.
That was a sharp Quad Kill!
Only PEEM remains!
Counter-push! Push now!
Stay calm.
Everyone, stay calm.
Guys, calm down.
Wait, wait!
Hey, what is PEEM doing?
I've got it! Told you I've got this.
We're in time!
Defend! Just hold them off.
(Deploying Super Creeps)
No, no, no!
Which is gonna break first,
their base or my head?
Whose base is going to break first?
Whoa, they've finally won
the final game.
Before my voice gave out,
the enemy base went down first.
And it ends with a victory
for Blue Viper.
That was absolutely impressive.
Sh*t,
that was so damn fun.
Exactly!
I'm not even sad.
Coming this far
is already a massive win for us!
To hell with what anyone else thinks.
We f*cking did our best.
We really gave it our all.
Playing with you guys was fun as hell.
I'm sorry, everyone.
I messed up several times today.
You don't need to be sorry.
Yeah.
Just the fact
that you took off that bear head
means we've already won.
You're the absolute best to me.
Well done.
You guys did a great job.
Can I give them a hug?
Dammit.
That's how you do it!
B.S. ...
- Brothers!
Let's go!
Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
Hello, everyone.
- I'm heading out first.
- What?
Where is he going?
Luckily, Peem carried the team.
Otherwise, the championship
would've slipped away.
You're just a sub.
Don't get too cocky.
Are you here to kick me
while I'm down?
If you're here to talk about
that f*cking bear head,
just leave.
I don't want to talk about it.
I actually believed you
about that bear head.
That's all you came to say?
Huh?
No.
Actually, I came to say...
congratulations.
If you're only saying that to be polite,
piss off.
That's not what I'm doing.
I really mean it.
The game is over,
and so is our status as rivals.
I just wanted
to congratulate you, buddy.
About what you told me...
that when the tournament is over...
we'd go back to being friends.
Don't you forget that.
Laem, over here!
Oh, I see.
It wasn't me! That wasn't me.
Don't stop yet.
Make some more noise!
Is this it?
Is this what you said
you'd prove to me and your mom?
I'm home.
How was it, son? Have you eaten yet?
Go ahead, Mom.
And how is your brother doing?
Well, he won his match today.
He should be in the final tomorrow.
I meant his life.
How has he been lately?
Is he doing okay?
He's fine.
Whether he's fine or not,
he's making six figures a month.
He has millions of followers, you know.
You should check it out, Mom, Dad.
Even though he's never said it,
he really wants both of you
to watch him compete.
I'm going to get some rest now.
- Go ahead, son.
- Okay.
(A lot of you have been asking me,)
("Why do you even compete?")
(Let me tell you
what my ultimate dream is.)
It's not about
the hundreds of thousands,
or the millions,
or any of those view counts.
Not at all.
(It's about getting a trophy...)
(to show off to my parents.)
(I just want to tell them,
"Look at your son,)
(the one who used to just
play games all day long.")
("He's a pro player now.")
(He's so good
he even became a national champion.)
(I just want them to be proud,)
so they can finally brag about me.
Wanna watch on the big screen?
I'll turn it on for you.
No need.
If I watch on the big screen,
I won't be able to send him donuts.
Look,
it's not a donut.
It's called donating, honey.
And that trophy you said
you'd bring home for us...
Whenever you get it,
bring it home for us to see.
Look at you, being such a crybaby.
You were amazing, Soh!
The way you made that comeback
was so cool.
Thank you so much
for joining B.S. Brothers.
Thank you very much.
Told you plenty of people like you.
You're amazing.
You okay?
Thanks.
Yeah, no problem.
That's what happens
when your friend gets too famous.
Too bad you didn't get to
bring a girl here on a date.
These past two days haven't been so bad.
Yeah, it would've been better
if Soh had won.
I didn't mean that.
I mean, being with you these two days
hasn't been bad at all.
Wait, look at that!
To my own MVP.
I want to have this MVP
by my side every season.
So, what exactly is going on
between you and Soh?
Soh...
is my boyfriend.
Boyfriend reveal!
I can't handle this!
- I can't.
- I...
also have a reward
for my amazing captain.
Since we've officially gone public,
I also want to introduce you to my mom.
What?
Thank you, P'Three.
For what?
The flowers?
That, too.
And thank you
for always staying by my side.
In the next APL tournament,
even if I don't have my bear head,
I won't be afraid anymore...
because I have
a source of confidence called P'Three.
Wow, look who's become a smooth talker.
Well, did your family head home already?
Yeah, they did.
They're probably home by now.
And how was it, seeing them today?
Better than winning the championship,
I guess.
I used to think all this time that...
I had to be number one first
for them to be proud of me.
But in reality,
they've been supporting me
from behind all along.
And I know there's another person
who's always supporting me, too.
Thank you, Soh.
♪You know I feel just a little bit♪
Hello?
Okay, sure.
Yes, will do.
♪Always been a dreamer,
will you dream with me?♪
♪If I should lose my way,
then would you follow me?♪
♪Always been a dreamer,
will you dream with me?♪
♪And if I stay like this,
then will you stay with me?♪
♪It burns like a fire♪
You're the cutest Support in the world.
And you're the captain
I love most in the world.
♪We've found love at last♪
♪Always been a dreamer,
will you dream with me?♪
♪If I should lose my way, then would you
follow me? (This too shall pass)♪
♪Always been a dreamer,
will you dream with me?♪
♪And if I stay like this,
then will you stay with me?♪
♪You know I feel just a little bit♪
♪Like I'm hypnotised♪
♪I don't know what I should make of it♪
♪Read between the lines♪
♪If you got out of the backseat of♪
♪This car with me,♪
♪If I told you what I'm thinking of,♪
♪Would you marry me?♪
♪I'm waking up slowly♪
♪Dreaming of a holy kiss♪
♪Always been a dreamer,
will you dream with me?♪
♪If I should lose my way,
then would you follow me?♪
♪Always been a dreamer,
will you dream with me?♪
♪And if I stay like this,
then will you stay with me?♪
♪We've found love at last♪
♪Always been a dreamer,
will you dream with me?♪
♪If I should lose my way, then would you
follow me? (This too shall pass)♪
♪Always been a dreamer,
will you dream with me?♪
♪And if I stay like this, then will you
stay with me? (We've found love at last)♪
♪Always been a dreamer,
will you dream with me?♪
♪If I should lose my way, then would you
follow me? (This too shall pass)♪
♪Always been a dreamer,
will you dream with me?♪
♪And if I stay like this,
then will you stay with me?♪